Guide to the Cornell University College of Architecture, Art, and Planning Records, 1905-2004
College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, Cornell University, Records, 1905-2004
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University College of Architecture, Art, and Planning records, 1905-2004
15-1-512
Cornell University. College of Architecture, Art, and Planning.
68.7 cubic ft.
Correspondence, applications, minutes, notices, announcements, reports, records, financial statements, postcards, blueprints, scale drawings, newspaper clippings, transcripts of talks, and pamphlets.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Contains administrative and historical records of the College of Architecture, Art, and Planning.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence concerning prospective students, applications for admission, requests for job information, requests for jobs to be filled, requests for professional information, professional and student societies, student prize competitions, complaints to Buildings and Grounds, the United States Mint, lecturers, applications for faculty and library positions, budgets, the College library, and personal and business correspondence of deans and professors. Other materials include minutes of the Committee on Student Conduct; Semi-Centennial Endowments items; bulletin board notices, fellowship announcements, accreditation reports, infirmary reports, grades, attendance lists, financial statements, postcards, blueprints, scale drawings, newspaper clippings, and miscellaneous pamphlets; clippings, correspondence, and other items pertaining to Margaret Bourke-White; list of the Clifton Beckwith Brown Memorial medalists (and blank medal) and the Charles Goodwin Sands Memorial medalists from 1900 to 1988, compiled by Professor Alexander Kira, and Sands medal (bronze), presented to Herbert P. Atherton, 1908. Also, transcripts of talks at 1977 Alumni Symposium by Robert Alexander, Edmund Bacon, Henry Tova, Jason Seley, Donald Greenberg, K. C. Parsons, Frank Rhodes, and students. Scrapbook of clippings and photographs relating to Frank Lloyd Wright, Dragon Day, and other activities.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. College of Architecture, Art, and Planning.; Bourke-White, Margaret, 1904-1971.; Atherton, Herbert P.; Reps, John William.; Alexander, Robert Evans, 1907-; Bacon, Edmund N.; Greenberg, Donald P. (Donald Peter), 1934-; Tova, Henry.; Rhodes, Frank Harold Trevor.; Seley, Jason, 1919-; Owings, Nathaniel Alexander, 1903-; Parsons, Kermit C. (Kermit Carlyle), 1927-; Cornell University. Buildings and Grounds Committee.; Cornell University. Committee on Student Conduct.; Cornell University. College of Architecture--Administration.; Cornell University. College of Architecture--Admissions.; Cornell University. College of Architecture--Endowments.; Cornell University. College of Architecture--Faculty.; Cornell University. College of Architecture--Finance.; Cornell University. College of Architecture--Funds and scholarships.; Cornell University--Buildings.; Cornell University--Libraries.
Subjects:
Architecture--Study and teaching.
Form and Genre Terms:
Architectural drawings.; Blueprints.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the archivist. Boxes 1-14 and 68 are not restricted.
Margaret Bourke-White items
All items can be found in Young's files except the item in Box 7:
Box 6, M B-W to Geo. Young, Dec. 27, 1927 - thanks for photographs (of Young's home)
Box 6, GY to B.S. Dalton, Dec. 27, 1927 - letter of intro. and recommendation as photographer
Box 6, GY to B.S. Hubbell Jr., same - both men in Cleveland
Box 7, M B-W to GY, July 15, 1929 - Would be glad to supply House Beautiful w. copies of photos of GY's house. (In Pthel Powers' file)
Box 8, GY to M B-W, Dec. 26, 1929 - thanks for Christmas greeting w. photograph Feb. 1, 1930
Box 8, Benj. S. Hubbell, Jr. to GY, sending clippings from Sunday [Cleveland] Plain Dealer, re: M B-W's work; entitled "Girl's Camera Is $25,000 Income." "She certainly has done a wonderful job and I hope the college will be fortunate in turning out, not only more girls like her, but also more men."
Additonal Information on Correspondence
White, Andrew Dickinson, 1832-1918
Correspondence ( June 17, 1912-June 23, 1913 ) of President White and C.A. Martin, Director of the Department of Architecture, regarding the Andrew D. White Competition for the design of a gateway for the main entrance to the north side of the campus and for a University auditorium and dining room; also Cornell Daily Sun clippings on the same subject. 1 folder, Box 1
White, Helen Magill, 1853-1944
Correspondence ( 1925-1927 ), mainly of Mrs. Andrew D. White, Goodhue Associates (New York City architects), F.H. Bosworth (Dean of C.U. College of Architecture), and Lee Lawrie (the sculptor) concerning the memorial to President White in Sage Chapel. 1 folder
Midjo, Christian Martinius Susseg, 1880-1973
Correspondence mainly between Midjo and George Young, Dean of the College of Architecture, while the former was studying and traveling in Europe. Inc. four ALS from Midjo, three from Florence ( Feb. 7, Mar. 7, Mar. 31, 1927 ) and from Copenhagen ( June 7, 1927 ), and carbons of Young's letters to Midjo and of Young's letters dealing with buisness he handled for Midjo during his absence. 1 folder, Box 6, Dec. 19, 1926-July 7, 1927
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Administrative/departmental files
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1896-1902 (Box 82)
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1902-09-1913-06 (Box 82)
  - Applicants for Admission A-Z, 1905-1910 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Exhibition, 1911-1912 (Box 1)
  - American Academy in Rome, Annual Report, 1911 (Box 1)
  - B[rochure] R[equests], 1911-1912 (Box 1)
  - A, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - American Institue for Architects, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - A.I.A. Central New York Chapter, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Appropriation Reports, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Architectural League of New York, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - B, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Beaux Arts Society, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Board of Trustees - C.D. Bostwick, Secretary, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Broucher Requests, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - C, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - City Planning, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Civil Engineering - Dean E.H. Haskell, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - College Art Association, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Columbia University, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Curriculum, Committee on, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - F, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - G, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Graduate School, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - H, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Hammond, Professor A.W., Secretary, University Faculty, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Hebrard, Jean, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - I-J, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Janitor, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - K, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Kellogg, Joseph M., 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Kellogg, Waldo S., 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - L, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - M, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - N-O, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Notices, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - P, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Pennsylvania, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Pittsburgh Architectural Club, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Prospective Students, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - R, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Registrar, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - S, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Shepard, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Special Studies, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Students, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - T, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Texas, University of, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Treasurer, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Tuition, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - University Secretary, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - V, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - W, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - White, Andrew D., 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - Y, 1912-1913 (Box 1)
  - A, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Ackerman, F.L., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture, Faculty of, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - A.I.A. Central New York Chapter, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - A.I.A. Committee on Education, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Announcements, copies of, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Appropriation Reports, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Architectural League of New York, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - A.C.S.A. Minutes, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - B, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Babcock, Professor Charles, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Beaux Arts Society, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Board of Trustees; E.L. Williams, Sec., C.D. Bostwick, Cashier, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Bossange, E.R., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Bristol, G.P., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - B[rochure] R[equests], 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - C, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Carnegie Institue of Technology, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Chapman, F. Burnham, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Civil Engineering - Dean Haskall, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Civil Service, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Columbia University, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Committee for the Survey of the Memorial of London, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Competition, Programs for, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - D, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Design 21 - Summer Problem of Professor Bossange, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Drafting Board Records, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Draftsmen Wanted, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - E, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Emer, H.G., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Entrance Drawing, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Examination Reports, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - F, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1913-09-1922-0 (Box 82)
  - Fellowships, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Franklin Hall, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - G, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - H, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Hammond, Professor A.W. - Secretary, University Faculty, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Horn, H.F., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - I-J, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - K, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Kellogg, J.M., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - L, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Library Council, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - M, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Malone, Wm. R. and J.D., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Marks, Summary of, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Marsh, Clinton S. re: son, H.P. Marsh, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Martin, C.A., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Morgan, George T., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - N-O, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Notices of Publications - summer, journal, news, etc., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - P, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Pennsylvania, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Professors of Design, Letters, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - R, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Registrar, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - S, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Schedule - College of Architecture, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Sheffey, Edward C., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Shreve, R.H., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Special Students, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Stillwell, Erle G., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Students Lists, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Summer Sessions, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Summer Sessions in Architecture, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - T, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Treasurers Wanted, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Treasurer, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - U-V, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - University Secretary, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - W, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Westervelt, J.C., 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - Y, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
  - A.C.S.A. Minutes, 1914-1915 (Box 3)
  - Prospective Students, 1914-1915 (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 1915-1916 (Box 3)
  - A.C.S.A. Minutes, 1915-1916 (Box 3)
  - Curriculum, Committee on, 1915-1916 (Box 3)
  - Prospective Students, 1915-1916 (Box 3)
  - Summer Competitions, 1915-1916 (Box 3)
  - A.I.A. Central New York Chapter, 1916-1917 (Box 3)
  - A.C.S.A., 1916-1917 (Box 3)
  - Curriculum, Committee on, 1916-1917 (Box 3)
  - Enlisted Students, 1916-1917 (Box 3)
  - Enlisted Students and leaves of absence, 1916-1917 (Box 3)
  - Prospective Students, 1916-1917 (Box 3)
  - A.C.S.A. Minutes, 1917-1918 (Box 3)
  - Beaux Arts Institute of Design, 1917-1918 (Box 3)
  - Curriculum for Juniors and Seniors, 1917-1918 (Box 3)
  - Prospective Students, 1917-1918 (Box 3)
  - Special Students, 1917-1918 (Box 3)
  - A, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Absenteeism, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Acting President - D.S. Kimball, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, College of, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - American Architect, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - A.I.A., 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - A.I.A. Central New York Chapter, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Armed Services - List of architects enlisted, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Armour Institute of Technology, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - A.C.S.A. Minutes, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - B, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - B.A.I.D., 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Board of Trustees, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Bool, H.J., 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - C, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Carnegie Institute of Technology - Bossange, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Civil Service, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Cornell Club - New York City, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - D, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - E, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - F, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - G, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - H, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Hubbell, B.S., Jr., 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - I, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - J, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - K, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - L, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - M, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Meeks, E.V., 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - N, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - O, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - P-Q, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Penn State College - A.L. Kocher, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - University of Pennsylvania - W. Plaird, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - President - J.G. Schurman, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Propective Students, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - R, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Registrar - Hoy, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Secretary, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Shreve, R.H. (firm of Carnegie and Hastings, NYC), 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Societe Des Architects, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Syracuse University - T.W. Revels, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - T, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Treasurer, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Trowbridge, A.B., 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - University Faculty, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - U-V, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - W, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Yearbook, 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - A, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - American Academy in Rome Annual Report, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - A.I.A., 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - A.I.A. Committee on Education, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - A.C.S.A., 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - B, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Beaux Arts Institute of Design, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Board of Trustees, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Boring, A.W., 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - C, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - City Planning, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Cornell University - Semi Centennial, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - D, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Draftsmen Wanted, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - E, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - F, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - G, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - H, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - I, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - J-K, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - L, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - M, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Medals (U.S. Mint - Philadelphia), 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - N, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - New York Trip, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Non Resident Lecturers, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Notices, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - P, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Pan-American Congress of Architecture, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - President (Schurman), 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Prospective Students, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - R, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Registrar, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - S - Includes corres. with R.K. Shreve, Walter King Stone, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Secretary, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Special Students, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - T, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - Treasurer, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - U-V, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - W, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - X-Y-Z, 1919-1920 (Box 4)
  - A, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Account Statement, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Agriculture, Faculty of, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - American Architectural Students Reconstruction Unit - R.C. Buell, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - A.C.S.A., 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of the Arts, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - A.I.A., 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Appropriations and monthly statements, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Arts and Sciences, Faculty of, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - B, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - B.A.I.D., 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - B.A.I.D. circuit exhibitions, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Board of Trustees, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - C, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Committee on Student Affairs, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - D, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Draftsmen Wanted, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - E, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - F, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - G, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - H, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Inventory, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - J, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - K, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - L, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Library, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - M, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Medals, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Notices, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - P, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - President, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Prospective Students, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - R, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Registrar, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - S, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Secretary, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Southern Intercolleigate Competition, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - T, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Teachers, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Treasurer, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - U-V, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - University Faculty, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - X-Y-Z, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Yale Alumni Weekly - Jan. 7, 1921, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
  - Alumni exhibition file, 1921-1922 (Box 5)
  - Architecture - Faculty minutes, 1921-1922 (Box 5)
  - A.C.S.A. Minutes, 1921-1922 (Box 5)
  - Semi - Centennial Letters re: alumni addresses, 1921-1922 (Box 5)
  - Semi - Centennial Committee, 1921-1922 (Box 5)
  - Trustee's acceptance for dinner Saturday, 1921-1922 (Box 5)
  - American Academy in Rome Annual Report, 1922-1923 (Box 5)
  - Application forms, 1922-1923 (Box 5)
  - Ashbee, C.R., 1922-1923 (Box 5)
  - A.C.S.A., 1922-1923 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1922-09-1928-06 (Box 82)
  - Pamphlet, 1922-1923 (Box 5)
  - Prospective Students, 1922-1923 (Box 5)
  - Student Records, 1922-1923 (Box 5)
  - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1922-1923 (Box 5)
  - A.C.S.A. Minutes, 1923-1924 (Box 5)
  - Heckscher Research Council Report, 1923-1924 (Box 5)
  - American Field Service Fellowships, 1924-1925 (Box 5)
  - A.C.S.A. Minutes, 1924-1925 (Box 5)
  - B.A.I.D., 1924-1925 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1924-1925 (Box 5)
  - General correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 5)
  - Schuchardt, W.H. - address at Eng. Society of Wisconsin, 1924-1925 (Box 5)
  - A.C.S.A. Articles of Organization, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Committee on Admissions, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Committee on Fine Arts, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - List of degree candidates, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Equipment, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Ithaca City Planning Commission, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Questionnaires and data, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Phi Kappa Phi - J.R. Collins, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Prospective Students, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Schuchardt, W.H., 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - Student Trip to Long Island, May 1926 (Box 5)
  - A, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Adminstrative Committee, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Agriculture, Faculty of, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - A.I.A., 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - A.I.A. Committee on Education - George C. Nimmons, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Arts and Sciences, Faculty of, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Art Association of Indiana, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - A.C.S.A., 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - B, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - B.A.I.D., 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - C, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Catholic University of America Year Book, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Committee on Education - Producer's Research Council, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Committee on Standardization and Purchase of Office Departmental Supplies, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Davis, E.G. (personal), 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Draftsmen Wanted, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Eidlitz, Robert, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - F, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Films, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - G, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Gargoyle, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Geberoux, E.W., 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - H-I-J, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Lawson, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - Library, 1926-1927 (Box 5)
  - M, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Martin, C.A., 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Midjo, C.M.S., 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - N-O-P, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Non-resident lecturers, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Notices, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Pendleton Fellowships, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Registrar, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - S-T, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Secretary, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Shreve, P.H., 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Teaching positions open, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Treasurer, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Trowbridge, A.B., 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - University Faculty, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - University Police, Committee on, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - W, 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - Young, George Jr. (personal), 1926-1927 (Box 6)
  - A, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Absences, vacation, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Agriculture, Dean Mann, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Alterations - White Hall, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - A.I.A., 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Applications for admission, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Applications for fellowships or scholarships, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Architecture, College of - new building, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Arts and Sciences Faculty, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - A.C.S.A., 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - B, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - B.A.I.D., 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Bosworth, F.H. (personal), 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Budget, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Catalogs (other schools), 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - C, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Committee on Purchase, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Comptroller - C.D. Bostwick, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Curriculum for College of Architecture, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Davis, E. Gorton, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Design Grades, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Drafting Room Space, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Draftsmen Wanted, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - E, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Exhibitions, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - F, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Fellowships or scholarships, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Fuertes Memorial Contest, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - G, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Gifts and Prizes - Baird, Dickinson, Brodie, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Graduate School, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Gutsell Press, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - H, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Honor System, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Inventory, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - K, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Landscape, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Library, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - M, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Martin, C.A. (personal), 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - M.I.T., 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Michigan, University of, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - N, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Notices, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - O, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - P, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Periodicals, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Prospective Faculty of Architecture, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - R, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Registrar, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - S, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Secretary, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Shreve, R.H., 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - T, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Teaching Positions Open, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Traveling Fellowship, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - Treasurer, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - U, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - University Faculty, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - University Poilce Committee, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - V, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - W, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - White, Mrs. Andrew D., 1925-1927 (Box 6)
    Correspondence with Dean F.H. Bosworth, Lee Lawrie, the sculptor, Bertman Grosvenor Assoc., architect, and others re: ADW Cenotaph in Sage Chapel
  - Young, George Jr. (personal), 1927-1928 (Box 6)
    Inc. copies of letters to Margaret Bourke White ( Dec. 7, 1927 ), and letters of recommendation for her to R.S. Dalton and B.S. Hubbell
  - Z, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
  - A, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Absences, Xmas, Easter, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Akerman, F.L., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Admission, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Athletic Association, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - American Academy of Rome, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - A.I.A., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - American Society for Testing Materials, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Announcements for, 1929-1930 (Box 7)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1928-1929 (Box 7)